<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>J R A</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on J R A</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:24:33 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post No7</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post-no7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:24:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post-no7/</guid>
      <description>On Acceleration: Am I an accelerationist? Most likely. I gotta be honest though, I haven&amp;rsquo;t really looked into the term very carefully. However, I think the term is pretty self-explanatory, so I will use it here the way I&amp;rsquo;ve heard it used lately. I believe that we should not be slowing down technological progress at almost any cost. The technological progress I&amp;rsquo;m talking about includes, progress in Energy, Medicine, Transportation, and Space Travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post No6</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post-no6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 19:32:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post-no6/</guid>
      <description>On Energy: We need better sources of energy. I&amp;rsquo;m glad to know Biden&amp;rsquo;s agenda considers this an important issue. The president&amp;rsquo;s Build Back Better plan, which also focuses on building, and the passage of the Inflation Reduction Act are good signs that the US government is taking some action on energy. Hopefully we can embrace this kind of movement regadless of what polical party is in office, because for the country to be able to defend its ideals of democracy and liberty, to fight climate change, and to solve important issues at home, it needs to not only have a strong economy but it also needs to build faster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post No5</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post-no5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 23:14:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post-no5/</guid>
      <description>On Finding Other Homes in the Solar System: Elon Musk is right. We do need to make sure we have humans living in other places other than earth at some point in the future. As many people have argued before, from Physicists to Science Fiction writers and those in between, such as Eric Weinstein and Musk, we need a plan B in case something goes wrong on earth. We need to preserve human life and the precious consciousness we are familiar with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post No4</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post-no4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:51:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post-no4/</guid>
      <description>On Building: &amp;ldquo;To build&amp;rdquo; is my current motto, or guiding principle. It is probably best summarized by Marc Andreessen&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Time to Build&amp;rdquo; essay, where he argues that our focus should be on building. I also think this is the best thing we can do right now to ensure a good future awaits us. And while I do think other things are important, such as tearing down oppresive systems and coming up with better, say, social programs (Yes, I lean left, but still centered), we are in great need of more building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post No3</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post-no3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 22:22:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post-no3/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday Night: &amp;ldquo;Erica Albright is a bitch. Do you think that&amp;rsquo;s because her family changed their name from Albrecht or do you think it&amp;rsquo;s because all BU girls are bitches? For the record, she may look like 34C but she&amp;rsquo;s getting all kinds of help from our friends at Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Secret. She&amp;rsquo;s a 34B, as in barely anything there. False advertising.
The truth is she has a nice face. I need to do something to take my mind off her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post No2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post-no2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 15:26:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post-no2/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts: I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how I&amp;rsquo;m going to name my new posts. Should I commit to simply numbering them forever? Or should I try to give each one a thoughtful title? Maybe I should only do that with longer posts&amp;hellip; I would have to label them somehow though. When I cross that bridge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post No1</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post-no1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 12:52:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post-no1/</guid>
      <description>Intro: Hello, world! This is my new blog site. I will try to share some thoughts and ideas in here. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking of making the posts super short - maybe a little twitter-like, which tells me a lot of people have considered this at some point&amp;hellip; Actually, I believe people used to use journals the way some people use twitter - that&amp;rsquo;s at least according to Steve Martin: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ttj5Nqof7Vw</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://example.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Submit the form below to get in contact with me.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
